Wow
It's so amazing, it's over
Now
Well, that's right
You will see four tiny holes.
yes, that's right
- Wow
- Oh
The main computer in the control room
To this main circuit in the vault
When a password command signal is sent,
This main circuit in this vault is
After creating a 16-digit password
Back to the main computer in the control room
I'm sending this
Then
The security officer in the security room
Come down here
with that password
This door of this safe room
How to open it
Eh, eh?
It's complicated.
- Yes
Control room main computer
Server connection completed
To the safe room main circuit
Password creation command
I also sent a signal
Password generation chip
What did you say it was?
security program
off
done
Now
password
832 0523 7882 06580
please
Is it open?
Okay
- wow
- Oh
Wow
Hey
There's one week left until D-Day
we made in it
Supernote 500 billion and
500 billion in this
I have to change it
Now
Go, go!
- like! Go, go
- Let's go.
-Go!
- Um
Nice to meet you, Mrs. Saimdang.
turn back
Ouch!
It's KC Bank
Team leader
Work while having a cup of coffee
Oh, coffee
Yoongyuya
-Who...
- Hey, it's Park Yun-gyu.
Uh, uh, uh!
Ugh!
thank you
Ah...
Mr. I
Ah, maybe I should quit drinking.
Write, ha
How much is left?
forward
Just need to raise 25 billion more.
Every morning, seven days a week
Even though I changed it, I couldn’t finish it all
Ugh, I have to do the first trimester on the same day.
- Huh?
-If there are this many people
You can change everything in 1 hour
Cheer up, come on
Come on, go, go
- Let's go.
- Okay
Go, go
Ah, yes, team leader.
Hey...
Can you see it?
Password 857 8538
It's 1005 83880
Hmm
- trash
- Oh, yes.
- Clean it up, okay?
- Yes, I understand.
Oh, yes, the security team.
Yes, in zone 1
I see some trash
Yes, please, please.
quickly, quickly
Fighting!
Ah, my brother
I was nervous because it was a tough job.
There is no one guarding it
Oh, fuck, what?
Everything into the ground
It must have crawled in.
Shall we take a closer look?
After
Oh, that...
Gaonna
One ad, you fucking thing
Put it in
Put it all in, Mr. Lee.
My group and I will go inside.
Group 2 is waiting here.
Team 3 brought a gas bomb?
Did you understand?
Yes, brother
Oh, yes, just a moment.
- Team leader
- Huh?
With security officials from the National Intelligence Service,
I want to talk on the phone
- From the National Intelligence Service?
- Yes
-Why?
- Well, I don't know.
Let’s take it once.
Yes, I changed my phone.
cash flow operation
Has it progressed?
No, not yet.
Well, after lunch, at 1 p.m.
This is a start, but why are you doing this?
Well, until we get there
stop transporting cash
Check the safe right now.
yes, i understand
Is there anything wrong?
- Yes
- Let's go down, quickly.
- Yes, I understand.
- You're watching.
- Now, the last one?
- Yes, this is the last one.
Come on, let's go.
What's going on?
My co-worker said he suddenly had diarrhea.
I was in a hurry to get in
Really?
But what kind of sweat
Does it flow like this?
Ha, I was originally
I have a bit of a fever.
What are you!
What are you doing here?
Ah, that's why I am like this
I wasn't going to do this
Ah, the bank is always the best
We're always together, okay?
What did I do wrong? yes?
Hmm
Transport personnel always wear hats
Don't you know?
Oh, I
Hey, I'm wearing a hat
Put it here, kid.
Well, the transportation time has changed.
Because the departure time was a little late
Go to the waiting room and rest.
Ah, yes, I understand, yes
Oh my, my, I'm sorry
Yes, let's take a look, okay?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, it's been a while since I last saw a hat...
- Boy...
- Mr. I
It's a friendly look for no reason
- Are you okay?
- Yes
What's going on?
How much is the total cash in transit today?
VIP customer worth 750 billion won
It even includes a rental safe.
Where is the previous new headquarters?
It's toward Gangnam Station.
mole, current location
To base camp
About 2km left
Timing is important
When you arrive at base camp
Kkangsuni starts climbing right away.
To break into the Seoul traffic central control room
How long does it take?
About 20 people?
When are you leaving for the gold mine?
I'm not sure yet
I think I'll leave after the search is over.
Now
Imminent departure for the gold mine
Mole Fast Movement
Here in three generations
Carrying 250 billion each
the other one
Loading with VIP customer rental safes
Then the inspection...
CCTV footage too
There was nothing special
The safe room has also been inspected.
- Can I take a look?
- Yes
boss
Arrived at base camp
Gangsuni, start climbing and fixer
Wait until contacted
See you at the top
Let's go
Now
You will receive it at once.
Why is this...
in three transport vehicles
Of the cash on board
Each worth 50,000 won
Please take out one bill at a time.
Why?
This is a report of counterfeit banknotes.
Oh, no way, it can't be
Why don't you like it?
Oh no
Okay
After
Take care of it
From the time the National Intelligence Service crawled in
I should have known, Han Soo-hyun.
It's all a joke with our set.
Are there 500 billion counterfeit bills?
Kid...
What is Han Soo-hyun doing now?
Skipping lunch too
sitting in the corner of the duty room
I'm not moving.
Because if you go, they will be interrogated harshly.
Feed me a lot of food
yes
- Not yet?
- Don't fuss.
Because it’s not something that can be done in a hurry
Stay, stay
ha
There are three underground bunkers in total.
Where is the entrance?
Which is the exit?
You are looking at the map in reverse.
This is Jongno side.
Because this is Majang-dong
Just around the corner
Are you coming out of the bunker?
Haha
- Fuck
- Oh, I'm sorry, bro.
Yeah, I didn't go to the military.
You son of a bitch, sure, Mr.
sorry
- Fixer, leaving in 16 minutes.
- After
Hey, 30m underground
There was a place like this
Is now the time to be amazed?
Just a little while
The gold horses are carrying 500 billion won
Come to the corner over there
Hey, anyway, my son let his guard down.
Spray it with gas bombs
We are taking 500 billion won
yes
Ah, why is this like this?
It's not even a power outage
Why is this happening?
Also, CCTV on the other side of the road.
Check it out by putting it on the screen.
Isn't it a big deal?
After
That's enough now
Well done
I'm doing this
Because it's for my sister
I really need to get rid of my sister.
don't worry
Everything has been said
ha
Ha, let's go
Gangsuni
Time required to reach the summit
Expected to take about 2 minutes
After
Holy shit
traffic light disturbance
The traffic light is coming. Irano, is this it?
Remote operation does not work
Why is this happening today?
It's a big deal
- Yes, now...
- Yes, it's not working.
yes
It's a full parking lot now, now.
Ugh
ha
At the Seoul Central Traffic Control Room
I noticed hacking
Control will be lost in one minute.
Kkangsuni sister, are you done?
- It's done.
- Everything has to be done.
Ugh...
Ouch!
Uh, ah...
Ugh
What is it? barely?
After
Uh, uh, mr.
Oh, sorry, this
Ah, this
There's too much traffic
I forgot
I fell asleep, what is this?
Oh, driving
How do you do it, really?
- Oh, what should I do with this?
- Wow, it's a neck.
Oh, this is for materials.
This is what I was trying to write
Ah, going to the hospital, ah...
Oh, I don't know, Mr.
- Now
- Wow
It's 5 million won.
It's money that won't go away, right?
Cash that even dogs will bite you if you give it to them
Ah, boss
You're so refreshing
- Thank you, yes.
- Yes, yes, yes
- No insurance, safe driving, yes.
- Yes
goodbye
yes, yes
Come on
I'm the Iron Curtain gangster.
If you hold on with all the strength in the world
Is there anything that can't be done?
Ugh!
Ugh
Oh!
Mr. Lee, this is ridiculous, Mr.
Ah, well, fuck, hey, quick, bounce, bounce!
child
Hey, Ma, clean it up.
ha
- Congratulations, brother.
- Shhh
ha
Wow
In the end, 500 billion won
Everything was taken away by Jang Jung-hyuk.
What are you going to do with my sister now?
without any money
my sister
How are you going to get it out?
That USB
Is it really that valuable?
I threatened you with this when I was smuggling, Mr.
Ha, Korean land
I was trying to get off safely, Mr.
Oh, what on earth is that?
no
Who are you threatening?
Who is it, the head of the National Intelligence Service?
National Intelligence Service, National Intelligence Service...
Incheon Container Terminal
For passing through the main gate
Create only one logistics invoice
Yes, yes, yes
on the road for hours
I'm wasting time
The road or my heart
It's frustrating all the same
Who is it because of?
Who are you?
KC Bank new headquarters
I'm the security officer.
Ah, yes
Did you arrive at the new headquarters safely?
cash van
Well, the cash is fine.
Loaded with VIP customer rental safe
There's a problem with the transport vehicle.
What's the problem?
That...
A rental safe was stolen.
Myeongseong Group Chairman Bang Geuk-hyun’s safe.
I'll be right there
Hey, drive to KC Bank’s new headquarters.
What's going on?
Chairman Bang Geuk-hyun of Myeongseong during transport.
The safe was broken into.
yes?
Yeah, uh!
Oh my, my, my, it's so good
- Grab it.
- Oh my, euchacha
Oh my, hey
Hey, hey
Oh my
Hey
Do you think he's going to die?
- Well, will that person survive?
- No
I won't die
Because I can't die
I keep living with that shit.
I mean
Even if you catch and eat one fish
The five internal organs are not touched.
That's me
It's a way to deal with people
This is my bullshit philosophy.
Huh? Borrow my money and take it
There are people who don't pay back, right?
Screw me so much that I won't die
Receive interest and principal
It's being released
Until the weight comes back
Now
Now, you have to move slowly.
Why not?
Ah, thank you
Ha, Mr.
Where are you going again?
why? Are you trying to follow me again?
yes
Hey
You have nothing to do
Following me
Isn't that tiring?
What did you do well?
Are you going to stand up and get angry?
Ah, if I am so untrustworthy
Have a child
Hey, Changseok!
- Yes
- You move with me.
- Me?
- 그래, 이 새끼야
창석아, 가, 빨리 가
가, 어
- 전화해
- 네
강남서에 연락해 봤어?
It's called loss of contact.
Jang Jung-hyuk, this bastard
In a state of no contact
My safety deposit box was stolen?
It would be a big deal if this got leaked.
Mr. Chairman, from the Financial Crimes Team of the National Intelligence Service.
I came to see the chairman.
Oh well, it’s still tomorrow
I was going to call the police.
I saw it pop up right away from the National Intelligence Service.
Uh, this is already
There was intelligence, right?
yes
Oh, director, are you okay?
I finished my round 3 weeks ago
I couldn't even contact you
Even if you don’t contact me
You will have a good time
Well, never mind.
Because he's a guy who plays well alone.
Huh, yeah
Usually VIP rental safes are
That's right, Chairman.
Something worth billions, tens of billions
diamonds or securities
Top-secret documents requiring security, etc.
By adding something like this
I know
In the Chairman’s VIP rental safe
It must have contained something quite important, right?
Well, paying expensive rental fees
You wouldn’t keep something that doesn’t matter, right?
During the KC Bank cash transportation operation
Counterfeit currency worth 500 billion won
It's like being replaced with pneumoconiosis.
I got intelligence
So while investigating
Chairman's rental safe
I found out that I was robbed.
for two incidents
until a connection is found
from our side
We're going to conduct a secret investigation.
Yes, the National Intelligence Service is handling the case.
I feel a little safer now, uh.
Hey, what did you say your name was?
Hmm, my name?
yes
It's Cha Tae
Ah, Agent Cha Tae's quick response.
I will tell the director.
Yeah, whatever you say.
Well, then, that’s enough.
- Yes, I do.
- Hmm
Ah, I need to eat one of these.
Ah!
Maybe...
Chairman
My name is Jang Jung-hyuk.
I'm the head of the Seoul Metropolitan Police's powerful team.
Do you know?
Jang Jung-hyuk...
Well, well
I think I've heard of it, yes.
Ah, I know so many people
We also meet
I'm not in a hurry right now
I can't remember.
This is what happens when you get to this age
yes
Sir, how far did the information leak out?
This now?
ha
Joong-ki!
yes
Yes, brother
I'm thirsty
If you drink that sea water
Will it work or not?
Uh...
It won't work
After drinking
You'll be thirstier, brother.
That's right
But I don't even know that
Since I was young
When I get thirsty, I can't hold back.
Whether it is sea water or muddy water
I had to drink it to relieve my anger.
yes
I drank to my heart's content
As expected
I was thirsty even more
The more you drink
That's what money is like
The more I have, the thirstier I become
I want more
Joong-ki
that money
I eat it all